<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<upcomingevents>
	<event>
		<title>Annual Day - 2015</title>
		<desc>M.S. Natyalaya was founded on 15th January, 2012.  Every year we celebrate our Annual Day during the second full week of January.  This includes the demonstration of skills acquired by the students during the previous year.  A few contests are conducted and exciting prizes.  Best dancers from all over Bangalore are invited as Judges to preside the contests.</desc>
		<when>15/01/2015</when>
		<where>Sri Kala Kalyana Mantapa Marriage Hall, Chinnapanahalli, Marathahalli, Bangalore</where>
	</event>
	<event>
		<title>Guru Day - 2015</title>
		<desc>M.S. Natyalaya was founded on 15th January, 2012.  Every year we celebrate our Annual Day during the second full week of January.  This includes the demonstration of skills acquired by the students during the previous year.  A few contests are conducted and exciting prizes.  Best dancers from all over Bangalore are invited as Judges to preside the contests.  This event is conducted both as an honour to the Guru as well as  a test to the students</desc>
		<when>16/11/2015</when>
		<where>Sri Raja Rajeshwari Auditorium Hall, 80ft Road, Koramangala, Bangalore</where>
	</event>
	<event>
		<title>Inter-School Day - 2015</title>
		<desc>M.S. Natyalaya was founded on 15th January, 2012.  Every year we celebrate our Annual Day during the second full week of January.  This includes the demonstration of skills acquired by the students during the previous year.  A few contests are conducted and exciting prizes.  Best dancers from all over Bangalore are invited as Judges to preside the contests.  We compete against other schools in the nearby area.  An impartial judge presides over the contest and awards the best dancers on stage in the end.  We've had a track record of winning this contest since inception.</desc>
		<when>5/6/2015</when>
		<where>Sri Kala Kalyana Mantapa Marriage Hall, Chinnapanahalli, Marathahalli, Bangalore</where>
	</event>
	<event>
		<title>Annual Day - 2016</title>
		<desc>M.S. Natyalaya was founded on 15th January, 2012.  Every year we celebrate our Annual Day during the second full week of January.  This includes the demonstration of skills acquired by the students during the previous year.  A few contests are conducted and exciting prizes.  Best dancers from all over Bangalore are invited as Judges to preside the contests.</desc>
		<when>15/01/2016</when>
		<where>Sri Kala Kalyana Mantapa Marriage Hall, Chinnapanahalli, Marathahalli, Bangalore</where>
	</event>
	<event>
		<title>Annual Day - 2015</title>
		<desc>M.S. Natyalaya was founded on 15th January, 2012.  Every year we celebrate our Annual Day during the second full week of January.  This includes the demonstration of skills acquired by the students during the previous year.  A few contests are conducted and exciting prizes.  Best dancers from all over Bangalore are invited as Judges to preside the contests.</desc>
		<when>15/01/2015</when>
		<where>Sri Kala Kalyana Mantapa Marriage Hall, Chinnapanahalli, Marathahalli, Bangalore</where>
	</event>
</upcomingevents>